{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"5694/84",
			"answer":"5694/84",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8899/73",
			"answer":"8899/73",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3665/50",
			"answer":"3665/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"8258/34",
			"answer":"8258/34",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4626/70",
			"answer":"4626/70",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"592.9/0.052",
			"answer":"592.9/0.052",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2699/0.055",
			"answer":"2699/0.055",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9.413/9.9",
			"answer":"9.413/9.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"195.1/50",
			"answer":"195.1/50",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2231/0.21",
			"answer":"2231/0.21",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}